Guide to the Professional Staff Congress/City University of New York Records and Photographs WAG.009
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series III: Records of the Professional Staff Congress, 1926-2009
  - Subseries III:B: Officers and Staff Files, 1926-2009
    - Sub Subseries III:B:4: Irwin Yellowitz Files, 1977-2009
      - Long-Term Care, 1990-1993 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Long-Term Care Committee, 1990-1992 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Membership Analysis, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Pension Committee, 1985-1987 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Phillips, George, 1988-1990 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Political Action (Mayoralty), 1989 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - PSC General, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - PSC General, 1990 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - PSC General, 1991 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - PSC General, 1992 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - PSC General, 1993 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - PSC General, 1994 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - PSC General, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - PSC General, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - PSC General, 1997 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Resident Professors (Bellush), 1986 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Retirees Chapter, 1998-1999 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Retirees Chapter, 1999-2000 (Box 47, Folder 21)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2000-Jun 2001 (Box 47, Folder 22)
      - Retirees Chapter, Feb 2001-May 2001 (Box 47, Folder 23)
      - Retirees Chapter, Jun 2001-Aug 2001 (Box 47, Folder 24)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2001-Dec 2001 (Box 47, Folder 25)
      - Retirees Chapter, Jan 2002-Aug 2002 (Box 47A, Folder 1)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2002-Jan 2003 (Box 47A, Folder 2)
      - Retirees Chapter, Feb 2003-Apr 2003 (Box 47A, Folder 3)
      - Retirees Chapter, May 2003-Aug 2003 (Box 47A, Folder 4)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2003-Dec 2003 (Box 47A, Folder 5)
      - Retirees Chapter, Jan 2004-Mar 2004 (Box 47A, Folder 6)
      - Retirees Chapter, Apr 2004-Aug 2004 (Box 47A, Folder 7)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2004-Feb 2005 (Box 47A, Folder 8)
      - Retirees Chapter, Mar 2005-Aug 2005 (Box 47A, Folder 9)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2005-Dec 2005 (Box 47A, Folder 10)
      - Retirees Chapter, Jan 2006-Aug 2006 (Box 47A, Folder 11)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2006-Aug 2007 (Box 47A, Folder 12)
      - Retirees Chapter, Sep 2007-May 2008 (Box 47A, Folder 13)
      - Retirees Chapter: Program Committee, 2002-2006 (Box 47A, Folder 14)
      - Retrenchment, 1992-1993 (Box 47A, Folder 15)
      - Search for Associate Executive Director, 1995 (Box 47A, Folder 16)
      - Search for Executive Director, 1995 (Box 47A, Folder 17)
      - Starling, Marion, 1991 (Box 47A, Folder 18)
      - Student Takeover, CUNY, 1991 (Box 47A, Folder 19)
      - Tax Deferred Annuities (TDA's): Halliday Program, 1984-1986 (Box 47B, Folder 1)
      - TDA's: Halliday Program, 1987-1989 (Box 47B, Folder 2)
      - TDA's: Van Raalte & Wagner Plan, 1984-1985 (Box 47B, Folder 3)
      - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (TIAA): NY State Contributions, 1991-1992 (Box 47B, Folder 4)
      - Teacher Recruitment Internship Project, 1985-1986 (Box 47B, Folder 5)
      - Treasurer/Finance Committee, 1986-1988 (Box 47B, Folder 6)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1977-1979 (Box 47B, Folder 7)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1980-1981 (Box 47B, Folder 8)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1981-1982 (Box 47B, Folder 9)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1982-1983 (Box 47B, Folder 10)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1983-1984 (Box 47B, Folder 11)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1984-1985 (Box 47B, Folder 12)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 47B, Folder 13)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1990-1999 (Box 47B, Folder 14)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 1999-2002 (Box 47B, Folder 15)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 2002-2003 (Box 47B, Folder 16)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund, 2003-2007 (Box 47B, Folder 17)
      - Zeller, Belle Scholarship Trust Fund: Audit and Liability Insurance, 1993-2008 (Box 47B, Folder 18)
    - Sub Subseries III:B:5: Belle Zeller Files, 1926-1989
      - Biographical, 1973-1986 (Box 47B, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, 1926-1958 (Box 47B, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1989 (Box 47B, Folder 21)
      - Events, 1972-1987 (Box 47B, Folder 22)
      - Writings and Statements, undated, 1973-1974 (Box 47B, Folder 23)
      - Writings and Statements, 1975-1976 (Box 47B, Folder 24)
  - Subseries III:C: General Files, 1969-1998
    - Academic Collective Bargaining Information Service, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Academic Freedom, 1972-1975, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Academics for Carey, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Adjunct Medical Plan, undated, 1980-1987 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Adjuncts, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Adjuncts, 1974-1975 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Adjuncts, 1976-1979 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Adjuncts, 1984-1990 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Affirmative Action: General, 1973-1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action: General, 1978-1982 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action: CUNY, undated, 1972-1974 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Affirmative Action: CUNY, 1975-1978, 1985 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Affirmative Action: Coordinators, undated, 1972-1976 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Affirmative Action: Savage v. Kibbee et.al., 1974 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Affirmative Action: Savage v. Kibbee et.al., 1975 (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - Affirmative Action: Savage v. Kibbee et.al. (I), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - Affirmative Action: Savage v. Kibbee et.al. (II), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 17)
    - Agency Shop, 1977-1979, 1986 (Box 48, Folder 18)
    - Agreements, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 19)
    - Agreements, 1977-1982 (Box 48, Folder 20)
    - American Association of Retired Persons (AARP), 1988-1989 (Box 48, Folder 21)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1972-1973 (Box 48, Folder 22)
    - AAUP, 1974-1977 (Box 48, Folder 23)
    - AAUP, 1978-1982 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - AAUP, 1984-1990 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - AAUP: Collective Bargaining Congress, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - American Council on Education, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - American Federation of Teachers/United Federation of Teachers (AFT/UFT), 1972-1977 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - AFT/UFT, 1978-1981, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - AFT/UFT: Higher Education Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - AFT/UFT: Standing Committee on Retirement, 1979-1992 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Arbitration Awards: Rubin Awards, 1972-1983 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Arbitration Cases, undated, 1972 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Arbitration Cases, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Arbitration Cases, 1974-1975 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Arbitration Cases, 1976-1981 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Arbitration Cases: Digest, undated (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Arbitration Cases: Digest, 1973-1975 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Arbitrations, 1980-1981 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Asbestos Problems, 1985-1988 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Bargaining (I), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Bargaining (II), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Bargaining (III), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Bargaining (IV), 1972 (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Bargaining, 1973 (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Bargaining, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Bargaining, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Bargaining, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Bargaining, 1977 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Bargaining: Transcripts (I), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Bargaining: Transcripts (II), 1977 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Bargaining, 1978-1985 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1974-1977 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Baruch College Chapter, 1980-1997 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Bilingual Education, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Black Colleges, 1979 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Board of Higher Education, undated, 1972 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Board of Higher Education, undated (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Board of Higher Education, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Board of Higher Education: Giardino, Alfred, 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Board of Higher Education: Minutes, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Board of Higher Education: Minutes (I), 1976 (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Board of Higher Education: Minutes (II), 1976 (Box 50, Folder 19)
    - Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) Chapter, 1972-1973 (Box 50, Folder 20)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 21)
    - BMCC Chapter (I), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - BMCC Chapter (II), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1978-1982 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1983-1988 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - BMCC Chapter, 1994-1997 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter, 1972-1973 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter, 1974-1976 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Bronx Community College Chapter, 1976-1987, 1994-1996 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Bronx Community College: Nursing Department, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, undated, 1972 (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter (I), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter (II), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1997 (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1978 (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Brooklyn College Chapter, 1979-1993 (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Brooklyn College: Productivity Study, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Budget Cuts, undated, 1973-1974, 1981 (Box 51, Folder 22)
    - Burks, David: Memorial Contributions, 1984-1985 (Box 51, Folder 23)
    - Calandra Institute, 1987 (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Campbell, Claude: Retirement Dinner, 1986 (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Campus Security, 1979-1980 (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Biographical Note, 1985 (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence, 1978 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence (I), 1979 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Cantor, Arnold: Correspondence (II), 1979 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Carey, Governor Hugh, 1974-1978 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Central Office Chapter, 1975-1990 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Chapters: General, undated, 1995-1997 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1974 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1974 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1977 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File, Mar 1977 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File, Apr 1977 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File, May 1977 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Chronological File, Jun 1977 (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File, Jul 1977 (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Chronological File, Aug 1977 (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Chronological File, Sep 1977 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Chronological File, Oct 1977 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1977 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1977 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1978 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Chronological File, Feb 1978 (Box 52, Folder 23)
    - Chronological File, Mar 1978 (Box 52, Folder 24)
    - Chronological File, Apr 1978 (Box 52, Folder 25)
    - Chronological File (I), May 1978 (Box 52, Folder 26)
    - Chronological File (II), May 1978 (Box 52, Folder 27)
    - Chronological File, Jun 1978 (Box 52, Folder 28)
    - Chronological File, Aug 1978 (Box 52, Folder 29)
    - Chronological File, Sep 1978 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Chronological File (I), Oct 1978 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File (II), Oct 1978 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Chronological File, Nov 1978 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Chronological File, Dec 1978 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Chronological File, Jan 1979 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - City College: Center for Biomedical Education, 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - City College: Center for Worker Education, undated (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - City College: Faculty Senate, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - City College: History Department Firings, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - City College: Review Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - City College: School of Engineering, 1972-1973 (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - City College: Women's Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - City College Chapter, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - City College Chapter, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - City College Chapter, 1974-1977 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - City College Chapter, 1980-1990 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - City College Chapter, 1991-1992 (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - City College Chapter, 1993-1997 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - City University of New York (CUNY) Academy for the Humanities and Sciences, 1981-1982 (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - CUNY: AIDS Policy, 1985 (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - CUNY: Board of Trustees, 1979-1981, 1989-1993 (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1977-1981 (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1982-1987 (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1990-1991 (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - CUNY: Budget, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis, undated, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (I), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (II), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis (III), 1975 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis Clippings, undated, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - CUNY: Budget Crisis Clippings, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1983 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1984 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1985 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1986-1987 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - CUNY Calendars, 1989 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - CUNY: Chancellor, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - CUNY: Chancellor, 1993-1995 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - CUNY: Contract Administration, 1974 (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - CUNY: Contract Administration Guideline, 1973 (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - CUNY: Disadvantaged Students, 1977 (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate, 1979-1981 (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1972-1975 (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1976-1978 (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - CUNY: Faculty Senate Minutes, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - CUNY: Governance, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - CUNY: Howe & Associates Report, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - CUNY: Instructional Staff, undated, 1972-1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - CUNY: Legislative Action Council, 1981 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - CUNY: Management, 1972-1975 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - CUNY: Master Plan, 1976, 1980, 1983 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - CUNY: Mission, 1978-1979 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - CUNY: Organizations, 1986 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - CUNY: Restructuring Proposals - Clippings, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - CUNY/PSC Relations: General, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - CUNY/SUNY Merger, 1976 (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - CUNY Support: Reception, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - CUNY: Vice-Chancellor's Office, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - CUNY Women's Coalition, undated, 1974-1977, 1980-1997 (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Civil Rights Act: Title VII, undated, 1972-1980 (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Civil Servant, 1985 (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Clarion, 1972-1978 (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Clarion, 1984-1989 (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Clarion Committee, 1973-1994 (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Clarion: Notes, undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Coalition Bargaining, undated, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, undated, 1972-1973 (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1974 (Box 55, Folder 25)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1975 (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education, 1976-1981 (Box 55, Folder 27)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education (I), 1994 (Box 55, Folder 28)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education (II), undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Kugler Papers, undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: National Center, 1975-1981, 1987-1990 (Box 55, Folder 31)
    - Collective Bargaining in Higher Education: Rabban Paper, 1994 (Box 55, Folder 32)
    - Collective Bargaining: SUNY Staff Survey, 1978 (Box 55, Folder 33)
    - College Laboratory Technicians (CLT) Chapter, 1972-1974 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - CLT Chapter, 1975-1976 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - CLT Chapter, 1977-1981, 1986 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1975-1977 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1978-1979 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - College of Staten Island Chapter, 1980-1988, 1994-1997 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University: Unions, 1985 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Commission on Academic Personnel Practice, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Commission on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1972, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Committee against Racism, undated (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Public Higher Education, 1986-1991 (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Educational Policy, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Community Colleges, 1973-1974, 1979-1989 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Comprehensive Education and Training Act (CETA) Program, 1975-1979 (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Computerization, 1974, 1976-1977 (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Conferences: General, 1978-1981 (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Cook, Beverly: "First Woman in Political Science", 1983-1984 (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Cooper, Sandi: "Who Rules Higher Education?", 1979 (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: General, undated, 1973-1980 (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: General, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: General, 1983-1986, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Chapter Chairpersons, 1972-1985 (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Members, 1976, 1980-1987 (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Cost of Higher Education, undated (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Council of Municipal Retiree Organizations (COMRO), 1981 (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Credit Union, 1980-1981, 1985-1989 (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - D'Amico, Samuel, 1974-1976 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Defense Fund, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - Deferral Payments, 1984-1987 (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - Delegate Assembly: Meetings, 1974-1978, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Delegate Assembly: Meetings, 1984-1990 (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - DeMelas, Anthony, 1973 (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Department Representatives, 1973, 1975 (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Discrimination: General, undated, 1972-1979 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Discrimination: against Women, undated, 1972-1980 (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Discrimination: against Women, 1982-1985 (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - Discrimination: against Gays and Lesbians, 1979-1985 (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Discrimination: against Persons With Disabilities, 1976-1981 (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - Discrimination: age Discrimination, undated, 1974-1980 (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - Discrimination: CUNY Report, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Discrimination Claims: Baruch College, 1973, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Discrimination Claims: Kingsborough Community College, 1975, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Discrimination Claims: Lehman College, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Discrimination Claims: Pace College, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Discrimination Claims: Queens College, undated, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Discrimination Claims: Queensborough Community College, undated, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Discrimination Claims: Staten Island Community College, 1973-1976 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Dissidents (PSC), 1973 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Doctoral Students Council, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Due Process, undated, 1975, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Dues, undated, 1973-1974, 1979-1981 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Elections: NYC, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Elections: PSC, undated, 1973, 1975-1976 (Box 57, Folder 14)
    - Elections: PSC, 1980-1985 (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, undated (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Elections and Credentials Committee, 1978-1989 (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Elections Committee: Appeals, 1986 (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - Emergency Fact Sheet, 1977 (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Enrollment, 1979 (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Equal Pay, 1972-1976 (Box 57, Folder 23)
    - Equal Rights Amendment, 1975-1979 (Box 57, Folder 24)
    - Evaluation, 1972-1979 (Box 57, Folder 25)
    - Ethics in Education (Newsletter), 1981 (Box 57, Folder 26)
    - Executive Council: Meetings, 1973-1977, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 27)
    - Executive Council: Meetings, 1984-1990 (Box 57, Folder 28)
    - Fact Finders Report I, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 29)
    - Fact Finders Report II, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 30)
    - Fact Finders Report III, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 31)
    - Fact Finders Report IV, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 32)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 1-12A), 1972 (Box 57, Folder 33)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 13-33) I, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 34)
    - Fact Finders Report (BHE Exhibits 13-33) II, 1972 (Box 57, Folder 35)
    - Fact Finders Report: Index to BHE Exhibits, 1972-1973 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Fact Finding Meeting (I), 1975 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Fact Finding Meeting (II), 1975 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Faculty Action, undated, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Faculty Development, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Faculty Evaluation of Administration, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Faculty Referral Service, 1976-1977 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Faculty Protection Act, 1979-1980 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education, 1974, 1978 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education (I), 1979 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education (II), 1979 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Federal Support for Higher Education, 1980-1981 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Finance Committee, 1976-1986 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Finances, 1976-1978, 1982, 1986 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Financial Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Financial Reports, 1976-1978 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Financial Reports, 1979-1983 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Financial Reports, 1984-1988 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Financial Reports, undated (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Financial Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1975-1977 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - Fiscal Crisis, 1978-1983, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, undated, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, 1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (I), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (II), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (III), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings (IV), 1976 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Fiscal Crisis: Clippings, 1977 (Box 59, Folder 6)